{"text":"function helloWorld() \n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  \n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  c\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  co\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  con\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  cons\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  conso\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  consol\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.l\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.lo\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log()\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"W\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"H\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"He\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hel\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hell\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello \")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello W\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello Wo\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello Wor\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello Worl\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!)\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!);\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\")\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\n\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nh\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhe\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhel\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhell\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhello\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhelloW\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhelloWo\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhelloWor\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhelloWorl\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhelloWorld\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhelloWorld()\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhelloWorld();\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object\n   containing all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object\n  \n  containing all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object\n  \n  \n  containing all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object\n  \n  \ncontaining all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object\n  \n  containing all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object\n  \ncontaining all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object\n  containing all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object\ncontaining all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an objectcontaining all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  \n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n\n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  \n\n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n     \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n     \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n     \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n     \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  c   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  co   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n     \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  c   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  co   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  con   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  cons   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  con   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  co   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  c   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n     \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  co   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  con   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  cons   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const o   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const ou   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const t   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const ty   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const typ   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const type   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const types   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const types    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const types =   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const types =    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const types = {}   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const types =   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const types    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const types   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const type   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const typ   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const ty   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const t   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const o   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const ob   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const obj   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const obje   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const objec   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object =   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object =    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {}   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n     \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  c   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  co   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  con   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  cons   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const a   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const ar   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const arr   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const arra   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array =   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array =    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = {}   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n     \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  c   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  co   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  con   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  cons   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const s   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const st   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const str   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const stri   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const strin   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string =   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string =    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string = \"\"   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string = \"s\"   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string = \"st\"   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string = \"str\"   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string = \"stri\"   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string = \"strin\"   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string = \"string\"   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string = \"string'\"   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string = \"string\";   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";     \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   c  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   co  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   con  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   cons  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const nu  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const num  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const numb  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const numbe  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number =  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number =   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 2  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  c  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  co  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  con  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  cons  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const b  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const bo  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boo  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const bool  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boole  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolea  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean =  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean =   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = t  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = tr  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = tru  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n    \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  c  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  co  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  con  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  cons  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const N  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const Nu  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nu  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nul  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null =  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null =   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null = n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null = nu  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null = nuu  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null = nuiu  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null = nulu  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null = nullu  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null = null;u  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null = null;\n  u  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null = null;\nu  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const null = null;\n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullV = null;\n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullVa = null;\n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullVal = null;\n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValu = null;\n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  c \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  co \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  con \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  cons \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const u \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const un \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const und \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const unde \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undef \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefi \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefin \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefind \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefine \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefined \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefined  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedV \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedVa \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedVal \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValu \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue =  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = i \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = u \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = un \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = und \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = unde \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undef \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefi \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefin \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefine \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined; \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  c \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  co \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  con \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  cons \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const no \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const na \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nan \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const N \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const na \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nan \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanV \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanVa \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanVal \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValu \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue =  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = n \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = N \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = Na \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n \n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;  \n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   \n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   r\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   re\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   ret\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   rety\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   retyr\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   retyrb\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   rety\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   ret\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   retu\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   retur\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{}\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \n\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \ns\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nsh\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nsho\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nshow\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nshowA\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nshowAl\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nshowAll\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nshowAllT\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nshowAllTy\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nshowAllTyp\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nshowAllType\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nshowAllTypes\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nshowAllTypes()\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;   return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n  \n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n  \n  \n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  c\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  co\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  con\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  cons\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  conso\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  consol\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.l\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.lo\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log()\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(t)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(ty)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typ)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(type)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeo)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof )\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof o)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof ob)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof obj)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof obje)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof objec)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof obj)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof ob)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof o)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof )\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof ob)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof obj)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof obje)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof objec)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, )\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, a)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, ar)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, arr)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, arrw)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, arrwa)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, arr)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, arra)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,s)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,st)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,str)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,stri)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,strin)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string,)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string,n)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, )\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, n)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, nu)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, num)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, numv)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, numve)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, num)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, numb)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, numbe)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, numberm)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, numberm )\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number,)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, )\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, b)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, bo)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boo)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, bool)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boole)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolea)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean,)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, )\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, n)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nu)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nul)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, null)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullV)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullVa)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullVal)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValu)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue,)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, )\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, u)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, un)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, und)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, unde)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undef)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefi)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefin)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefind)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinde)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefin)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefine)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefined)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedV)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedVa)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedVal)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValu)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue,)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, )\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, n)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, na)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nan)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanV)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanVa)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanVal)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValu)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue)\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";   const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n     return{};\n \nshowAllTypes();\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhelloWorld();\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = {\"one\" \n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = {\"one\"\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = \n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = ;]]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [;]]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [;]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = []\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1, \"two\" : 2]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1, \"two\" : ]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1, \"two\" :]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1, \"two\" ]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1, \"two\"]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1, \"two]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1, \"tw]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1, \"t]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1, \"]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1, ]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1,]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : 1]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" : ]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" :]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\" ]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one\"]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"one]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"on]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"o]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{\"]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [{]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = []\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = []]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [1];]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [1,];]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [1,2];]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = ;\n  const array = [1,2];]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [1,];]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [1];]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = \"string\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = \"strig\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = \"strg\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = \"stg\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = \"sg\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = \"g\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,t array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,ty array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typ array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,type array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeo array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array ,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number, boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean, nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue, undefinedValue, nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue, undefinedValue,typeof nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue, undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [a];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [ar];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arr];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrr];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrra];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrray];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrray1];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrray1,];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrray1, ];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrray1, a];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrray1, ar];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrray1, arr];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrray1, arra];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrray1, array];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [arrray1, array2];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array ]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[]]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] ]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] =]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] = ]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] = {}]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[]  = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] a = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] ar = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] arr = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] arra = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] array = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] arr = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] ar = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] a = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[]  = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] = {};]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] = {;]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] = ;]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[] = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array[ = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [\"\"];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [\"];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];]\n  const string = g\";\n  const number =11;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object,typeof  array typeof ,string,typeof  number,typeof  boolean,typeof  nullValue,typeof  undefinedValue,typeof  nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const arraiy = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const arraiuy = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const helloWorld = require('../../exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world');\n\ndescribe('hello world function', () => {\n  test('should log \"Hello World!\" to the console', () => {\n    const consoleSpy = jest.spyOn(console, 'log');\n    helloWorld();\n    expect(consoleSpy).toHaveBeenCalledWith('Hello World!');\n    consoleSpy.mockRestore();\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex1.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  \n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  c\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  co\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  con\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  cons\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const \n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const r\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const re\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const ret\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const retu\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const retur\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const return\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const return \n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const return  \n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const return =\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const return = \n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const return = {}\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const return = l}\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const return = ;l}\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n}\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n}\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n  \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n}\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n  \n  \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n}\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n\n  \n  \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n}\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n\n\n  \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n}\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n}\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const return = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n}\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const return = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const return = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const retrn = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const retr = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const ret = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const re = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const r = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const  = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const c = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const co = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const cod = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.loge);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logte);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtye);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtype);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypee);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeoe);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeofe);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof e);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof ce);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof coe);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof code);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof codee);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof codee);\n    \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof codee);\n}  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof codee);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;\n \n  console.logtypeof codee);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;\n \n  console.logtypeofcodee);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;\n \n  console.logtypeocodee);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;\n \n  console.logtypecodee);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;\n \n  console.logtypcodee);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;\n \n  console.logtycodee);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;\n \n  console.logtcodee);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;\n \n  console.logcodee);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;\n \n  console.logtypeof codee);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof codee);\n  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof codee);\n}  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof codee);\n    \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof codee);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeofe);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logte);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.loge);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;}\n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  const code = ;\n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);\n    \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);\n  \n    \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);\n  \n  \n    \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);\n\n  \n    \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);\n\n\n    \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);\n\n   \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);const code = ;\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = ;\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = {typeof object, typeoarray, string, number, boolean, nullValue undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = {typeof object, typeofarray, string, number, boolean, nullValue undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = {typeof object, typeof array, string, number, boolean, nullValue undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = {typeof object, typeoarray, string, number, boolean, nullValue undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = ;\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = t;\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = ty;\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = typ;\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = type;\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = typeo;\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n  console.logtypeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValuee);  const code = typeof;\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n ;  const code = typeof;\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n \n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n c\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n co\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n con\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n cons\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n conso\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n consol\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.l\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.lo\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log()\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(x)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(xx)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(xcx)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(xcox)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(xx)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(x)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(cx)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(cox)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(codx)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(codex)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n /console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof \n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof t\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof ty\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof typ\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof type\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof typeo\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof typeof\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof typeof{}\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof typeof;\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\n\n     console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\n\n   console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\n\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\nv\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\nconst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\nconst code = typeofconst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\n  const code = typeofconst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\nconst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\nvconst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\nvc  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\nvc    onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\nc    onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\n  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof typeof;\n  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof typeof\n  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\n  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeo;\n  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = type;\n  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typ;\n  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ty;\n  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = t;\n  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n  onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n    onst code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n    onst code = ttypeofypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n    onst code = ttypeoftypeofypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n  onst code = ttypeoftypeofypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n  onst code = ttypeof typeofypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n ypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\nypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = t;\nypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ty;\nypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typ;\nypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = type;\nypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeo;\nypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\nypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  ypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  cypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  coypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  ypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  \n  ypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  \nypeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  \neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  c\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  co\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  con\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  cons\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const \neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const c\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const co\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const cod\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const co\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const c\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const \neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  cons\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  con\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  co\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  c\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  \neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  co\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  con\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  cons\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  conso\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  consol\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.l\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.lo\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log()\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(y)\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(t)\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(ty)\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(typ)\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(type)\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(typeo)\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(typeof)\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(typeof )\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(typeof c)\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(typeof co)\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(typeof cod)\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(typeof code)\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  \n  \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  \n  \n  \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n  \n  \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n\n  \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeo;\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = type;\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typ;\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ty;\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = t;\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = { npm run test:easyobject, array, string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, boolean, nullValue, undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, nullValue, undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof:object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typeof code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof:object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typeofcode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof:object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typeocode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof:object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typecode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof:object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(typcode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof:object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(tycode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof:object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(tcode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof:object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.log(code);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof:object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.logcode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof:object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof:object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.logtypeof ccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, typeof:undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.logtypeof ccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, undefined, typeof:nanValue};\n\n \n  console.logtypeof ccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, typeof:nullValue, undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  console.logtypeof ccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, typeof:boolean, nullValue, undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  console.logtypeof ccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, typeof:number, boolean, nullValue, undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  console.logtypeof ccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, typeof:string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  console.logtypeof ccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = {typeof: object, typeof:array, string, number, boolean, nullValue, undefined, nanValue};\n\n \n  console.logtypeof ccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n\n \n  console.logtypeof ccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n\n \n  console.logtypeofccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n\n \n  console.logtypeoccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n\n \n  console.logtypeccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n\n \n  console.logtypccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n\n \n  console.logtyccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n\n \n  console.logtccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ;\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = t;\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = ty;\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typ;\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = type;\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeo;\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  \n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  c\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  co\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  con\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  cons\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  constc\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const \n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const c\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const co\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const cod\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code1\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code=\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code \n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code =\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = \n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = t\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = ty\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typ\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = type\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeo\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[a]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[ar]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[arr]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[arrr]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[arrrr]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[arrarr]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[arrayrr]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[array]r]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[array];r]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[array];\n  r]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[array];\nr]\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof;\n  const code = typeof[array];\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof\n  const code = typeof[array];\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof \n  const code = typeof[array];\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof typeof[array];\n  const code = typeof[array];\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof  typeof[array];\n  const code = typeof[array];\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof + typeof[array];\n  const code = typeof[array];\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array];\n  const code = typeof[array];\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof && typeof[array];\n  const code = typeof[array];\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array];\n  \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array];\n\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array];\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; &\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & t\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & ty\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typ\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & type\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeo\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof{}\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof &\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & t\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & ty\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typ\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & type\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeo\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof{}\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof &\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & t\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & ty\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typ\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & type\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeo\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof{}\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof &\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & t\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & ty\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typ\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & type\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeo\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof{}\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof &\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & t\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & ty\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typ\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & type\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeo\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof{}\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof &\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & t\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & ty\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typ\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & type\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeo\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof \n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeofL\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeofP\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof{}\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof;\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array];  typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof;\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof;\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof;\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array];  typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof;\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]; typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof;\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array] typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof;\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array]  typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof;\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n \n //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);;  const code = typeof & typeof[array] & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof;\n\n\n \n  console.logccode);\neof\n console.log(codex;)\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof & typeof[array] & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof & typeof;\n\n\n\n  console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof\n\n\n  console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;u\n\n\n  console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;u\n\n  console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;u\n  \n\n  console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  \n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhelloWorld();\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\nconsole.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\nconsole.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  module.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\nconsole.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n    module.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    module.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"Hello World!\");\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"Hello World!);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"Hello World);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"Hello Worl);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"Hello Wor);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"Hello Wo);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"Hello W);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"Hello );\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"Hello);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"Hell);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"Hel);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"He);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"H);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\");\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"n);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"na);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"nam);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"name);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"name\");\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"name\"0);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"name\"));\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"name\");\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(\"name);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(name);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(nam);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(na);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(n);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log();\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(s);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(sc);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(scr);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(scre);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(screm);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(scremN);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(scremNa);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(scremNam);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(scremName);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(scremName());\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(scremName(n));\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(scremName(na));\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(scremName(nam));\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(scremName(name));\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\nconsole.log(screamName(name));\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m \n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m c\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m co\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m con\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m cons\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const \n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const s\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const sc\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scr\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scre\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const screa\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream \n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream =\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = \n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = S\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = Sc\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = Scr\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = Scre\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = Screa\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = Scream\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = ScreamN\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = Screa\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = Scre\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = Scr\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = Sc\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = S\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = \n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = s\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = sc\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = scr\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = scre\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screa\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = scream\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamN\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamNa\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamNam\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName()\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName(n)\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName(na)\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName(nam)\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName(name)\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName(name);\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName(nam);\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName(na);\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName(n);\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\n\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nc\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nco\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\ncon\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\ncons\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconso\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsol\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.l\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.lo\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log()\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(s)\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(sc)\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(sce)\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scea)\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(sceam)\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(sce)\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(sc)\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scr)\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scre)\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(screa)\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream)\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n na\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n nam\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name \n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name =\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = \n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name \n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name =\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = \n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = na\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = nam\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = name\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = na\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = n\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = \n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = \"\"\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = \"n\"\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = \"na\"\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = \"nam\"\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = \"name\"\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = \"name\";\n\n\n    m const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\nodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n\n  \n}\n\nhelloWorld();\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n name = \"name\";\n\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\nconsole.log(scream);\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \nconsole.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \nconsole.log(scream);console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(scream);console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(screa);console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(scre);console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(scr);console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(sc);console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(s);console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log();console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(n);console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(na);console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(nam);console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);console.log(scream);\n\n  \n}\n const scream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolesream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescrream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreaream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamBream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamBBream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamBNBream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamBream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamNBream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamNaBream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamNamBream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamNameBream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamName()Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamName(\"\")Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consolescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);consol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);cool\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);col\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  col\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  cool\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  conol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  consol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  constol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const sol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const scol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const scrol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const screol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const screaol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const scrol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const scol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const sol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const naol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const namol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUppol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUppeol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpperol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper =ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = nol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = naol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = namol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = nameol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.tol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.tool\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUppol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUppeol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCaol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCasol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCaseol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase()ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  col\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  cool\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  conol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  consol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  constol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const naol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const namol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameSol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScrol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScreol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScreaol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScreamol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream =ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = naol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = namol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameIol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUppol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUppeol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpperol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper +ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"\"ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\"ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\":ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  col\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  cool\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  conol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  consol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  consool\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  consolol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  consoleol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.lol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.lool\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.logol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log()ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(n)ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(na)ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nam)ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(name)ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameS)ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameSc)ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScr)ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScre)ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScrea)ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream)ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  rol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  reol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  retol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  retyol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  retyrol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  retol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  retuol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  returol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  returnol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return ol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nnol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nanol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return namnol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return namenol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nameSnol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nameScnol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nameScrnol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nameScrenol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nameScreanol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nameScreamnol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  console.log(name);c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nameScream;nol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \nc\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nameScream;nol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n c\n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nameScream;nol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n \n  const nameUpper = name.toUpperCase();\n  const nameScream = nameUpper + \"!!!\";\n  console.log(nameScream);\n  return nameScream;nol\nescreamName(\"John Doe\");Bream = screamName();\n\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n  \n  console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n\n  console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  \n  \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n  \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n\n\n  \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nc\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nco\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\ncon\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\ncons\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst \n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst c\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst co\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst cod\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code()\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code \n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code =\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = \n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = {}\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, typeof nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = \n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type/of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = \n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type//of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = \n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n\n\n  \n  \n  \n  \n}\n \n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n\n\n  \n nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN;\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = \n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\n\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\no\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\na\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\nar\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narr\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narra\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narray\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narray:\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narray:t\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narray:ty\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narray:typ\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narray:type\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narray:typeo\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narray:typeof\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narray:typeof[]\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narray:typeof[];\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ;\narray:typeof[],\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = \narray:typeof[],\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\n\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\ns\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nst\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstr\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstri\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstrin\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:t\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:ty\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typ\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:type\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeo\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof'\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\"\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\".\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\n\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\n\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\n\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\n\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\n\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof Na\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n nanValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n nValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \nnpm run test:easy Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n \nValue = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  /const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  /const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  /const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  //const string = \"\";\n  const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  //const string = \"\";\n  /const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  //const string = \"\";\n  //const number = 1;\n  const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  //const string = \"\";\n  //const number = 1;\n  /const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  //const string = \"\";\n  //const number = 1;\n  //const boolean = true;\n  const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  //const string = \"\";\n  //const number = 1;\n  //const boolean = true;\n  /const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  //const string = \"\";\n  //const number = 1;\n  //const boolean = true;\n  //const nullValue = null;\n  const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  //const string = \"\";\n  //const number = 1;\n  //const boolean = true;\n  //const nullValue = null;\n  /const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  //const string = \"\";\n  //const number = 1;\n  //const boolean = true;\n  //const nullValue = null;\n  //const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  //const string = \"\";\n  //const number = 1;\n  //const boolean = true;\n  //const nullValue = null;\n  //const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  /const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nconst code = ,\narray:typeof[],\nstring:typeof\"\",\nnumber:typeof 1,\nboolean:typeof true,\nnullValue:typeof null,\nundefinedValue:typeof undefined,\nnanValue:typeof NaN\n\n  \n  //const object = {};\n  //const array = [];\n  //const string = \"\";\n  //const number = 1;\n  //const boolean = true;\n  //const nullValue = null;\n  //const undefinedValue = undefined;\n  //const nanValue = NaN; \n  Value = NaN;\n\n  \n\n  //console.log(typeof object, typeof array, typeof string, typeof number, typeof boolean, typeof nullValue, typeof undefinedValue, type///of nanValue);\n  const code = typeof;\n\n console.log(code);\n\n  return{};\n}\nshowAllTypes();\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}